healthtalk.org 2016-12-10

# Privacy policy | healthtalk.org

## Our policy

DIPEx (which expression includes “healthtalkonline”, “youthhealthtalk”, “we”, “us”, “our”) respects your right to privacy and this statement is intended to identify the ways in which we collect and intend to use the personal and other information that you transmit when you visit the site to enable us to provide material that gives a useful service.

## Collection of Information

On the Healthtalkonline website, in order to make the site more responsive to your and other users' requirements, we use "cookies" (the information sent from a web server to your browser identifying which internet sites you have visited) to enable us to tailor the site's content to your interests. We may also use cookies to track the pages of the site that are most visited to identify which are of most interest. You can set your browser not to accept cookies, but if you do we will be less able to provide a service that most closely matches your needs.

## Use of Information

We will use the information provided by you within DIPEx for the purposes specified in this Privacy Statement but will not sell, trade or rent the information we get from you to any third parties without consent. We may, however, disclose such information where it is necessary to comply with the law, or to enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions of Use or to protect our rights and those of other site users. DIPEx complies with the UK Data Protection Act 1998. All information collected from you is password-protected for storage purposes within a database controlled by us. We cannot absolutely guarantee the security of the database or that the information you supply to us will not be intercepted over the Internet. Any information you post in the website may be available to anyone with Internet access. We may use personal data for the provision of demographic information of an aggregated and collective nature for our own analysis of commercial trends, site usage and other similar research and statistics. We may share this with third parties in an anonymous format that does not allow you to be identified.  
Please read be thoughtful about information you make available online and we recommend you read the [User Guidelines](http://healthtalkonline.org/terms-and-conditions-use).

## Change of Policy

If we need to change our privacy policy at any point, we will post changes on this page.

## Contacting us

If you would like to alter the way in which we process your personal information, please contact us using our contact form.
